Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS 202
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Ephemera
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 158)
      SoHo News reproduction - 9 April 1980
      Bomb Magazine reproduction
      Body Politic K. Anger Cover - April 1982
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 159)
      Cepa Gallery Postcard
      Aperture Magazine portrait
      Art et Industrie ad
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 160)
      Talking Heads reproductions and materials
      New York Rocker Talking Heads cover
      New York Rocker Brian Eno cover
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 161)
      Esquire article
      New York Magazine clipping - 12 December 1988
      Actuel tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 162)
      Vile cover
      Washington Project for the Arts: Punk art clippings
      Valentin Tatransky review
      Jimmy de Sana c.v. from catalogue
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 163)
      File Megazine clipping - Fall 1979
      Zeit Magazine clipping - October 1979
      Bomb Magazine tearsheet
      Stefanotty ad tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 164)
      Terence Sellers / Jimmy De Sana interview
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 165)
      Oggi Domani flyer
      Omni Magazine tearsheet - March 1983
      Village Voice clippings - 26 January 1988
      File Megazine tearsheet - Spring 1976
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 166)
      Arts Magazine - May 1989
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 167)
      Postcard
      Marincola essay tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 168)
      Bomb Magazine Cover - Winter 1988
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 169)
      Village Voice clippings - 8 May 1978
      Artifacts At The End of A Decade - 1981
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 170)
      File Megazine cover - Fall 1977
      File Megazine tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 171)
      Image Scavengers clippings
      $bfat image
      Bomp Magazine cover - March 1979
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 172)
      American Photographer tearsheet - March 1984
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 173)
      American Photographer article - December 1983
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 174)
      Village Voice Clippings - 26 January 1988
      Exhibition Postcards (2)
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 175)
      Postcards (2)
      HK City Magazine article July 1988
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 176)
      Giant Light Bulb reproduction
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 177)
      Auto-Portraits Pompidou Center catalogue
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 178)
      Sweatshit reproduction
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 179)
      Two Holograms
      Roberta Smith NY Times Review - 29 January 1988
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 180)
      New York Contemporary Art Observer April 1988
      Vanity Fair Clippings
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 181)
      USF Galleries Pamphlet
      New Voices 2
      'You're the guy I want to share my money with" flyer
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 182)
      Art in America clippings
      Downtown cover
      Gusto Review
    - Title: (Box 73, Folder 183)
      New York Newsday - 24 Nov 1987
      Oggi Domani postcard
      Anderson-Giorno-Burroughs album
- Series XIV: Objects
  A collection of photographic equipment and props.
  - Cameras, lenses, filters and accessories (Box 74)
  - Film loaders; agitator (Box 75)
    Description: Photographic equipment
  - Developing tubes with two lids; easel (Box 76)
  - Baby doll, rubber stamps, polaroid products (Box 77)
    Description: Assortment of objects including doll, JDS Trust stamps, unprocessed film rolls, Marilyn Minter video, film strips
- Series XV: Media
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Access Restrictions
    Access copies may not be available at this time. Please see a Fales archivist.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    Original media is generally not available for researcher use. Please see a Fales archivist for access.
    - De Sana Home Movie - Daytona - Oceanarium, 1954 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0001)
      Format: 16mm film
      Length: 50ft
    - De Sana Home Movie - Daytona Beach, 1954 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0002)
      Length: 50 ft
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, circa 1959 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0003)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, circa 1959 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0004)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, circa 1951 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0005)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, circa 1956 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0006)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, circa 1953 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0007)
  - Subseries C: Videotape
    - Marilyn Minter 100 FOOD PORN (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0008)
      Format: VHS
      TRT: 00:30:00
- Oversize Series II: Photographic prints by theme
  - Subseries E: Portrait
    20x24 silver gelatin prints
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 186)
      Delight, Duca
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 186)
      Greathouse, Timothy
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 186)
      Unknown Subject
  - Subseries F: Miscellaneous
    20x24 silver gelatin and color C prints
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 184)
      Bed (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 184)
      Plastic Bags (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 184)
      Shoes (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 185)
      Toothpaste (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 185)
      Bubblegum (Silver Gelatin Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 185)
      Flour (Color C Print)
- Oversize Series XIII: Ephemera; clippings, reproductions, advertisements
  - Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      Danceteria Ad (2)
      13-1/2x19 Moquette
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      Mask Print
      13-1/2x19
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      Wrong wrong
      15x25 Poster
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      James White and the Blacks record sleeve, was originally the last item in the sequence devised for this subseries by Jimmy de Sana.